<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Docs on LonerHermitNEET</title><link>http://localhost:1313/docs/</link><description>Recent content in Docs on LonerHermitNEET</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 07:07:07 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Exploring the Efficacy of Independent Learning: An Informal Comparative Analysis with Formal Education</title><link>http://localhost:1313/docs/self-directed-learning/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/self-directed-learning/</guid><description>Exploring the Efficacy of Independent Learning: An Informal Comparative Analysis with Formal Education#Introduction:#I wonder&amp;hellip; Is the stay-at-home person who studies with the same study material with the same work ethic, intelligence level, motivation, consistency, and flexibility just as effective as a student attending a prestigious college?
Comparative Look:#Let&amp;rsquo;s say for example, that Stay-at-home Person studies textbooks and gains a lot of knowledge by studying articles, textbooks, and all sorts of studies, whether it be Asian studies, history, politics, economics, psychology, philosophy, geography, the arts, musical instruments, drawing, writing (fiction and non-fiction), dancing, singing, and all sorts of theory.</description></item><item><title>Deeper Dive into Audience Engagement: An Informal Case Study of Two Fantasy Narratives</title><link>http://localhost:1313/docs/post1/comparative-analysis-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/post1/comparative-analysis-1/</guid><description>Deeper Dive into Audience Engagement: An Informal Case Study of Two Fantasy Narratives#Introduction:#It has been said time and time again that narratives can be either trendy or niche, with some narratives outside a popular genre breaking boundaries of what constitutes a compelling story to a particular audience; making determining viability of a narrative to reach an expected level of success challenging and dependent on a host of factors, the numbers of which can be difficult to obtain without editorial participation of the authors&amp;rsquo; part.</description></item><item><title>Matthew Status Report #1</title><link>http://localhost:1313/docs/matthew-status-report-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/matthew-status-report-1/</guid><description>Matthew Status Report #1#Good evening, everyone.
To start, the following images are the current stats with respect to the viewership decrease in the range between Chapter 1 and 2 and the range between Chapter 5 and 10 of the story currently titled &amp;ldquo;Matthew: The Epitome of Grace and Beauty - Intellectual LitRPG Isekai Novel&amp;rdquo;. (This is subject to change.)
Moreover, the first round of revisions starting from Chapter 1 to the current latest chapter is undergoing heavy consideration.</description></item></channel></rss>