<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>LonerHermitNEET</title><link>http://localhost:1313/</link><description>Recent content on LonerHermitNEET</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 07:07:07 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Antipolo: Ascent of the Exceptional - Open-World City Fantasy Novel</title><link>http://localhost:1313/books/Antipolo/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/books/Antipolo/</guid><description>Antipolo: Ascent of the Exceptional - Open-World City Fantasy Novel#Book Description:#The city itself becomes a character, a complex and ever-changing landscape that both shapes and is shaped by the lives of its inhabitants. From the struggles of the working class to the power plays of the elite, the story delves into the personal stories and aspirations of its diverse cast as they grapple with trauma, rebuild their communities, and confront deep-seated tensions bubbling beneath the surface.</description></item><item><title>Mark: Tainted Ambition - Sociopath LitRPG Fantasy Novel</title><link>http://localhost:1313/books/Mark/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/books/Mark/</guid><description>Mark: Tainted Ambition - Sociopath LitRPG Fantasy Novel#Book Description:#Follow Mark, a young man devoid of empathy, on his ruthless quest for power. Haunted by a traumatic past, he uses his charm and cunning to manipulate and climb the social ladder, leaving destruction in his wake.
From a humble villager to a feared bandit lord and eventually a ruler of cities, Mark&amp;rsquo;s relentless pursuit of dominance knows no bounds.</description></item><item><title>Matthew: The Epitome of Grace and Beauty - An Intellectual Psychological Isekai LitRPG</title><link>http://localhost:1313/books/Matthew/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/books/Matthew/</guid><description>Matthew: The Epitome of Grace and Beauty - An Intellectual Psychological Isekai LitRPG#Book Description:#Matthew, a once ordinary man, had his life abruptly snatched away. Despite a content existence on Earth, surrounded by loved ones and knowledge, he found himself thrust into a new world, devoid of care or compassion. Struggling to adapt, he relied on his intellect to navigate the chaos around him. Every action held consequence, with death lurking at every turn.</description></item><item><title>Exploring the Efficacy of Independent Learning: An Informal Comparative Analysis with Formal Education</title><link>http://localhost:1313/articles/self-directed-learning/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/self-directed-learning/</guid><description>Exploring the Efficacy of Independent Learning: An Informal Comparative Analysis with Formal Education#Introduction:#I wonder&amp;hellip; Is the stay-at-home person who studies with the same study material with the same work ethic, intelligence level, motivation, consistency, and flexibility just as effective as a student attending a prestigious college?
Comparative Look:#Let&amp;rsquo;s say for example, that Stay-at-home Person studies textbooks and gains a lot of knowledge by studying articles, textbooks, and all sorts of studies, whether it be Asian studies, history, politics, economics, psychology, philosophy, geography, the arts, musical instruments, drawing, writing (fiction and non-fiction), dancing, singing, and all sorts of theory.</description></item><item><title>Deeper Dive into Audience Engagement: An Informal Case Study of Two Fantasy Narratives</title><link>http://localhost:1313/articles/comparative-analysis-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/comparative-analysis-1/</guid><description>Deeper Dive into Audience Engagement: An Informal Case Study of Two Fantasy Narratives#Introduction:#It has been said time and time again that narratives can be either trendy or niche, with some narratives outside a popular genre breaking boundaries of what constitutes a compelling story to a particular audience; making determining viability of a narrative to reach an expected level of success challenging and dependent on a host of factors, the numbers of which can be difficult to obtain without editorial participation of the authors&amp;rsquo; part.</description></item><item><title>Matthew Status Report #1</title><link>http://localhost:1313/articles/matthew-status-report-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/matthew-status-report-1/</guid><description>Matthew Status Report #1#Good evening, everyone.
To start, the following images are the current stats with respect to the viewership decrease in the range between Chapter 1 and 2 and the range between Chapter 5 and 10 of the story currently titled &amp;ldquo;Matthew: The Epitome of Grace and Beauty - Intellectual LitRPG Isekai Novel&amp;rdquo;. (This is subject to change.)
Moreover, the first round of revisions starting from Chapter 1 to the current latest chapter is undergoing heavy consideration.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid><description>Time zone: GMT+8
Interests: Bodybuilding Playing musical instruments such as: Violin Piano Fingerstyle guitar Recorder Cajon Djembe Dancing Serializing fiction stories Writing regularly in my autobiography and journal Singing Making music Drawing Coding Reading textbooks</description></item></channel></rss>