<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Books on LonerHermitNEET</title><link>http://localhost:1313/books/</link><description>Recent content in Books on LonerHermitNEET</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 07:07:07 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Antipolo: Ascent of the Exceptional - Open-World City Fantasy Novel</title><link>http://localhost:1313/books/Antipolo/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/books/Antipolo/</guid><description>Antipolo: Ascent of the Exceptional - Open-World City Fantasy Novel#Book Description:#The city itself becomes a character, a complex and ever-changing landscape that both shapes and is shaped by the lives of its inhabitants. From the struggles of the working class to the power plays of the elite, the story delves into the personal stories and aspirations of its diverse cast as they grapple with trauma, rebuild their communities, and confront deep-seated tensions bubbling beneath the surface.</description></item><item><title>Mark: Tainted Ambition - Sociopath LitRPG Fantasy Novel</title><link>http://localhost:1313/books/Mark/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/books/Mark/</guid><description>Mark: Tainted Ambition - Sociopath LitRPG Fantasy Novel#Book Description:#Follow Mark, a young man devoid of empathy, on his ruthless quest for power. Haunted by a traumatic past, he uses his charm and cunning to manipulate and climb the social ladder, leaving destruction in his wake.
From a humble villager to a feared bandit lord and eventually a ruler of cities, Mark&amp;rsquo;s relentless pursuit of dominance knows no bounds.</description></item><item><title>Matthew: The Epitome of Grace and Beauty - An Intellectual Psychological Isekai LitRPG</title><link>http://localhost:1313/books/Matthew/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/books/Matthew/</guid><description>Matthew: The Epitome of Grace and Beauty - An Intellectual Psychological Isekai LitRPG#Book Description:#Matthew, a once ordinary man, had his life abruptly snatched away. Despite a content existence on Earth, surrounded by loved ones and knowledge, he found himself thrust into a new world, devoid of care or compassion. Struggling to adapt, he relied on his intellect to navigate the chaos around him. Every action held consequence, with death lurking at every turn.</description></item></channel></rss>